(electronic typing)
- [Messy Mya] What happened
at the New Wil'ins?
(music starts)
Bitch, I'm back,
by popular demand.
- [Beyoncé] Y'all haters corny
with that Illuminati mess.
Paparazzi, catch my
fly and my cocky fresh.
I'm so reckless when I
rock my Givenchy dress.
(Stylin')
I'm so possessive,
so I rock his Roc necklaces.
My daddy, Alabama.
Mama, Louisiana.
You mix that negro with that Creole,
make a Texas bama!
I like my baby heir with
baby hair and afros.
I like my negro nose with
Jackson Five nostrils.
Earned all this money,
but they never take the country out me.
I got hot sauce in my bag, swag.
- [Messy Mya] Ooh! Yeah, baby.
Oh yeah, I-- ooh!
Oh yes, I like that.
(music resumes)
- [Big Freedia] I did not
come to play with you, hoes.
(laughs)
I came to slay, bitch!
I like cornbreads and
collard greens, bitch.
Oh yes!
You best'a believe it.
- [Beyoncé] Y'all haters corny
with that Illuminati mess.
Paparazzi, catch my
fly and my cocky fresh.
I'm so reckless when I
rock my Givenchy dress.
(Stylin')
I'm so possessive,
so I rock his Roc necklaces.
My daddy, Alabama.
Mama, Louisiana.
You mix that negro with that Creole,
make a Texas bama!
I like my baby heir with
baby hair and afros.
I like my negro nose with
Jackson Five nostrils.
Earned all this money,
but they never take the country out me.
I got hot sauce in my bag, swag.
I see it, I want it (want it).
I stunt, yellow-bone it (bone it).
I dream it, I work hard,
I grind 'til I own it (own it).
I twirl on them haters (haters),
albino alligators (gators).
El Camino, with the seat low,
Sippin' Cuervo with no chaser (chaser).
Sometimes I go off (I go off).
I go hard (I go hard).
Get what's mine (take what's mine).
I'm a star (I'm a star).
Cause I slay (slay), I slay (hey)
I slay (okay), I slay (okay)
All day (okay), I slay (okay)
We gon' slay (slay), gon' slay (okay)
We slay (okay), I slay (okay)
I slay (okay), okay (okay)
I slay (okay), okay, okay, okay, okay!
Okay ladies, now let's get in formation.
(Cause I slay)
Prove to me you got some coordination.
Slay trick, or you get eliminated.
When he fuck me good, I
take his ass to Red Lobster.
(Cause I slay)
When he fuck me good, I
take his ass to Red Lobster.
(We gon' slay)
If he hit it right,
I might take him on a
flight on my chopper.
(I slay)
Drop him off at the mall,
Let him buy some J's, let him shop up.
(Cause I slay)
I might get your song
played on the radio station.
(Cause I slay)
I might get your song
played on the radio station.
(Cause I slay)
You just might be a black
Bill Gates in the making.
(Cause I slay)
I just might be black
Bill Gates in the making!
I see it, I want it (want it).
I stunt, yellow-bone it (yellow-bone it).
I dream it, I work hard,
I grind 'til I own it (own it).
I twirl on my haters (haters),
albino alligators (gators).
El Camino, with the seat low,
Sippin' Cuervo with no chaser.
Sometimes I go off (I go off).
I go hard (I go hard).
Take what's mine (take what's mine).
I'm a star (I'm a star).
Cause I slay (slay), I slay (hey)
I slay (okay), I slay (okay)
We gon' slay (slay), gon' slay (okay)
We slay (okay), I slay (okay)
I slay (okay), okay (okay)
I slay (okay), okay, okay, okay, okay!
Okay ladies, now let's get in formation.
(Cause I slay)
Prove to me you got some coordination.
Slay trick, or you get eliminated.
(I slay)
Okay ladies, now let's get in formation.
You know you that bitch,
when you cause all this conversation.
Always stay gracious,
best revenge is your paper.
(siren wailing)
- Girl, I hear some thunder.
(thunder cracks)
- Golly! Look at that water, boy!
Whoo! Lord!